<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Easthrees Studio</title><link>https://zhuchb.github.io/easthrees-blog/</link><description>Recent content on Easthrees Studio</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 16:56:04 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://zhuchb.github.io/easthrees-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://zhuchb.github.io/easthrees-blog/posts/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 16:56:04 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://zhuchb.github.io/easthrees-blog/posts/privacy-policy/</guid><description>Introduction Our privacy policy will help you understand what information we collect at [Company/AppName], how [Company/AppName] uses it, and what choices you have. [Company/AppName] built the [AppName] app as a free app. This SERVICE is provided by [Company/AppName] at no cost and is intended for use as is. If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation with this policy. The Personal Information that we collect are used for providing and improving the Service.</description></item><item><title>Hello World</title><link>https://zhuchb.github.io/easthrees-blog/posts/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 12:19:32 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://zhuchb.github.io/easthrees-blog/posts/hello-world/</guid><description>This is a post for test</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://zhuchb.github.io/easthrees-blog/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zhuchb.github.io/easthrees-blog/about/</guid><description>Illustration from Victor Hugo et son temps (1881) The Hunchback of Notre-Dame (French: Notre-Dame de Paris) is a French Romantic/Gothic novel by Victor Hugo, published in 1831. The original French title refers to Notre Dame Cathedral, on which the story is centered. English translator Frederic Shoberl named the novel The Hunchback of Notre Dame in 1833 because at the time, Gothic novels were more popular than Romance novels in England.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://zhuchb.github.io/easthrees-blog/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zhuchb.github.io/easthrees-blog/contact/</guid><description>This is an example of a custom shortcode that you can put right into your content. You will need to add a form action to the shortcode to make it work. Check out Formspree for a simple, free form service.
Your Name Email Address An email address is required. Message</description></item></channel></rss>